

ENGINEERING GRADUATE · FULL STACK DEVELOPER · CODING HOBBYIST

159 Yorkland Street, Richmond Hill, ON, Canada, L4S1C5

□ (647) 621-6600 | susean17@my.yorku.ca | seans98 | seansu98

About

An electrical engineering graduate with 1 year of software development experience and a strong aptitude to learn. Seeking entry level software engineering/development positions

Skills

Front-End Development ReactJS (Redux, MaterialUI), HTML, JavaScript (Vanilla, JQuery), CSS (Bootstrap) **Back-End Development** Node.js/ExpressJS, EJS, Python (functional and object-oriented), RESTful APIs

Database Development SQL (MySQL), NoSQL (MongoDB, Mongoose)

QA and Testing Postman
Version Control Github

Other Languages C, C++, Java, Bash, Verilog, VHDL

Spoken Languages Spanish (Intermediate), English (native)

Projects_

Web-Based Energy Management System

Toronto, Canada Sept 2020 - April 2021

Engineering Capstone (ENG 4000)

• Quality Assurance Lead and Backend engineer for developing a web-based energy management system (EMS)

- Collaborated with a team of engineering students in creating an extensive Python simulation, which simulates several energy systems including Battery-Energy Storage Systems, Multi-Unit Residential Buildings, and EV chargers + their car-flow
- Created a backend Python cost calculator that projects future costs for EV charging costs, inputs such as inflation, vehicle maintenance and electricity cost trends were considered
- Debugged code and stress tested the simulation using Postman

Doorbell ProjectToronto, Canada

EMBEDDED SYSTEMS (EECS 3215)

January 2020 - April 2020

- Created a Doorbell with a remote chime using the LPC 802 Microcontroller for the Embedded Systems term project
- The project contained two sensors and two actuators for input/output
- Programmed the Microcontroller in C for functionality and connections to external peripherals

Work Experience ____

Quality Assurance Co-op Student

Mississauga, Canada

CERTAINTEED GYPSUM

April 2019 - August 2019

- Maintained the backend of the Quality Index Database (QI) using Microsoft Access
- Collaborated with managers and leads to restructure web drivers for the company
- Created Standard Operating Procedures (SOP's) outlining the features of the QI Database
- Created weekly quality index reports

Rides Operator

Canada's Wonderland

Vaughan, Canada

April 2016 - August 2018

- Operated rides in a safe and guick manner
- · Performed daily maintenance checks on rides
- Collaborated with fellow crew members to ensure guest safety and satisfaction
- Attended to guest needs to ensure park enjoyment

Education

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng) in Electrical Engineering

Toronto, Canada

LASSONDE SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING, YORK UNIVERSITY

Expected June 2021